couponit.com 2018-03-25

# Couponit.com - Privacy Policy

[Home](http://www.couponit.com/) > Privacy Policy   
  
Couponit.com is committed to providing you with quality service and a great online shopping experience. As a result, we have created this privacy policy to address your privacy concerns. 

Any inquiries regarding this privacy policy can be directed through our contact form found at:  
<http://www.couponit.com/contact.html>  

**Information We Collect:  
**Couponit.com does not collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc. unless it is voluntarily submitted by our visitors. We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent, and will never give or sell your information to third parties without your permission.

**Site Usage Tracking  
**Couponit.com may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. In addition to cookies, Couponit.com collects other information which is not personally identifiable. This includes information on your web browser, your screen resolution, your geographic location, the type of computer you're using, and which web page you came from. This information is collected in order to improve your browsing experience, and help provide you with more relevant content.

**Usage of IP Addresses  
**Couponit.com may use your IP (Internet protocol) address for several reasons. These include helping diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, and to provide you with content with content which is tailored to your needs.

**Links To External Web Sites  
**Couponit.com offers links to many web sites who's content and policies we are not able to control. While we try to link only to reputable web sites, we recommend that you read the individual privacy policies of sites which we may link to, as Couponit.com cannot be held liable for the actions of these sites.
